{
	"ComiQuestions" : {
		"1" : {
			"question" : "______ have been developed specifically for pipelined systems.",
			"option1" : "Utility software",
			"option2" : "Speed up utilities",
			"option3" : "Optimizing compilers",
			"option4" : "None of the mentioned",
			"answer" : "Optimizing compilers"
		},
		"2" : {
			"question" : "What is the high speed memory between the main memory and the CPU called?",
			"option1" : "Register Memory",
			"option2" : "Cache Memory",
			"option3" : "Storage Memory",
			"option4" : "Virtual Memory",
			"answer" : "Cache Memory"
		},
		"3" : {
			"question" : "RISC stands for _______",
			"option1" : "Restricted Instruction Sequencing Computer",
			"option2" : "Restricted Instruction Sequential Compiler",
			"option3" : "Reduced Instruction Set Computer",
			"option4" : "Reduced Induction Set Computer",
			"answer" : "Reduced Instruction Set Computer"
		},
		"4" : {
			"question" : "The fetch and execution cycles are interleaved with the help of _______",
			"option1" : "Modification in processor architecture",
			"option2" : "Clock",
			"option3" : "Special unit",
			"option4" : "Control unit",
			"answer" : "Clock"
		},
		"5" : {
			"question" : "Any condition that causes a processor to stall is called as _____.",
			"option1" : "Hazard",
			"option2" : "Page Fault",
			"option3" : "System Error",
			"option4" : "None of the abover",
			"answer" : "Hazard"
		},
		"6" : {
			"question" : "In the ARM, PC is implemented using _____",
			"option1" : "Caches",
			"option2" : "Heaps",
			"option3" : "General purpose register",
			"option4" : "Stack",
			"answer" : "General purpose register"
		},
		"7" : {
			"question" : "Whenever the data is found in the cache memory it is called as _____",
			"option1" : "HIT",
			"option2" : "MISS",
			"option3" : "FOUND",
			"option4" : "ERROR",
			"answer" : "HIT"
		},
		"8" : {
			"question" : "The number of sign bits in a 32-bit IEEE format is ____",
			"option1" : "1",
			"option2" : "11",
			"option3" : "9",
			"option4" : "23",
			"answer" : "1"
		},
		"9" : {
			"question" : "The situation where in the data of operands are not available is called ______.",
			"option1" : "Stock",
			"option2" : "Stuctural Hazard",
			"option3" : "Data Hazard",
			"option4" : "Deadlock",
			"answer" : "Data Hazard"
		},
		"10" : {
			"question" : "The transfer between CPU and Cache is _______",
			"option1" : "Block Transfer",
			"option2" : "Word Transfer",
			"option3" : "Set Transfer",
			"option4" : "Associative Transfer",
			"answer" : "Word Transfer"
		}
	}
}